Guide to the Planned Community Archives collection, 1960-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 11: Oversized 1960-2010
  - Adjustment Recess and Projection Details, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Revised Pedestrian Underpass-Site Plan, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Plan and Details, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Pedestrian Underpass Details, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Unit D17, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Building D-Units D13 and 14, Roof Framing Plan Part 1, Second Floor Framing Plan Part 1, Framing Plan Part 4, First Floor Framing Plans for Typical Units, First Floor Framing Part Plan Over Community Center Auditorium, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Roof Over Supermarket, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Building C-Foundation Plan, Sections and Details, First and Second Floor Framing Plan, Foundation Plan, Sections and Details, Roof Framing Plan South, Ground Floor Plan, Foundation Sections, Foundation Plan, Sections and Details, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Building H-East, West, Foundation Plan East and West, First Floor, Edge-Band, Foundation Plan, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Balcony Details for Unit A and C, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Building K-Framing Plans, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Building L-Framing Plans, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Lake Wall Plans, Details 1-7, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Box Flume Plan and Details, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Overlook Tower Plans and Details, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Topographical Maps (2), 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 2)
  - Reston First Village Center-Building F Plans, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 3)
  - Reston First Village Center-Building D Plans, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 3)
  - Building G-Roof Plan and Machine Room M108, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Ground FLoor Plan E101, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Ground Floor Plan E102, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-First Floor Plan E103, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-First Floor Plan E104, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Typical Floor Plan (2nd thru 5th) E105, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Typical Floor Plan (2nd thr/5th) E106, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Roof Plan and Elevator Equipment Room E107, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Telephone, First Alarm, and Intercom Risers E108, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-TV Risers and Schedules E109, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Electrical Risers and Schedules E110, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Underfloor Plan M101, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Ground Floor Plan M102, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-First Floor Plan M103, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-2nd and 3rd Floor Plan M104, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-4th Floor Plan M105, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Typical Floor Plan (5th thru 14th) M106, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-15th Floor Plan M107, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Flow Diagram M109, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Riser Diagram M110, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Plumbing Riser Diagram, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Ground Floor Plan E101, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Ground Floor Plan E102, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-First Floor Plan E103, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-First Floor Plan E104, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 4)
  - Building G-Typical Floor Plan (2nd thru 14th)E105, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Typical Floor Plan (2nd thru 14th)E106, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-15h Floor Plan E107, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Roof Plan and Elevator Equipment Room E108, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Parking Structure Plan E109, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Telephone, Fire Alarm, and Intercom Risers E110, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-TV Risers and Schedules E112, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Electrical Risers and Schedules E112, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Underfloor Plan M101, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Ground Floor Plan M102, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-First Floor Plan M103, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Typical Floor Plan (2nd thru 13th)E104, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Typical Floor Plan (14th)M105, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-15th Floor Plan M106, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Roof Plan and Machine Room M107, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Parking Structure and Underfloor Plan M108, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Flow Diagram M109, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Riser Diagram M110, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Building G-Riser Diagram M111, 1980 (Box Mapcase 2, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 84, Block 1B1, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 84, Block 1B2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 39, Block 9, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 64, Block 1B, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 908, Block 5, Lot 10, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 909, Block 4, Parcel 4, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 84, Block 1A, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 84, Block 1B, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 73, Block 5, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 908, Block 4, Lot 2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Section 908, Block 3, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 1)
  - Reston Blueprints-Development Plans, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Terminal Systems, Section 905, Block 2A, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Planting Plans, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-J.B. Enterprises, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Washington West Quadrangle (Map), 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Reston (Map), 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Map, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Map, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Reston Business Park (Drawing), 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Plot Plan, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Drawing, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 2)
  - Reston Blueprints-Plaza America: Building 2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-2100 Reston Avenue, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-South Lakes Mobil, Section 80, Block 5A, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-McDonalds, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-Taco Bell, Section 909, Block 5, Lot 4, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-Warner Cable of Reston, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-1801 Alexander Bell Drive, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-United Virginia Bank Branch, Commerce Park Two, Section 900, Block 5, Lot 1, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-Pracon Office Building, Section 908, Block 5, Lot 1, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-Herndon Concrete, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-W.H.G.A. Office Building, Section 908, Block 5, Lot 2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-Kinder Care Learning Centers, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-Chevron USA, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 3)
  - Reston Blueprints-Plaza America: Building 2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-2100 Reston Avenue, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-South Lakes Mobil, Section 80, Block 5A, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-McDonalds, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-Taco Bell, Section 909, Block 5, Lot 4, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-Warner Cable of Reston, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-1801 Alexander Bell Drive, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-United Virginia Bank Branch, Commerce Park Two, Section 900, Block 11D3, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-Pracon Office Building, Section 908, Block 5, Lot 1, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-Herndon Concrete, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-W.H.G.A. Office Building, Section 908, Block 5, Lot 2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-Kinder Care Learning Centers, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-Chevron USA, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 4)
  - Reston Blueprints-Plaza America: Building 2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-2100 Reston Avenue, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-South Lakes Mobil, Section 80, Block 5A, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-McDonalds, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-Taco Bell, Section 909, Block 5, Lot 4, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-Warner Cable of Reston, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-1801 Alexander Bell Drive, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-United Virginia Bank Branch, Commerce Park Two, Section 900, Block 11D3, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-Pracon Office Building, Section 908, Block 5, Lot 1, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-Herndon Concrete, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-W.H.G.A. Office Building, Section 908, Block 5, Lot 2, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-Kinder Care Learning Centers, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Reston Blueprints-Chevron USA, 1980 (Box Mapcase 3, Folder 5)
  - Unmarked Black Binder #1: Reston Promotional Ads, 1978-1981 (Shelf 1, Binder 1)
    This binder contains multiple advertisement clippings, pamphlets, and fliers from the late-1970s and early-1980s. Among them are ads promoting land and house sales, government and private sector jobs moving to Reston, and Reston's mix of natural beauty and industry. Copies of the Reston Residential Land Sales newsletter are also included in this binder.
  - Unmarked Black Binder #2: Early Reston Promotional Ads, 1969-70 (Shelf 1, Binder 2)
    This binder contains multiple advertisement clippings from the early days of Reston. Among them are ads promoting land and house sales, Reston's attractive system of public transportation and the many ammenities it had such as golf, tennis, horseback riding, among others. One ad also claims that "Reston was concerned with the environment before environment became a concern."
  - Unmarked Black Binder #3: Reston Promotional Ads, 1980s (Shelf 1, Binder 3)
    This binder contains multiple advertisement clippings from the 1980s. Among them are ads promoting Reston as a unique place, close to D.C. but much different than its central city. These ads call attention to Reston's natural surroundings, low population density and the availability of sporting activities. Some ads also highlight Reston's 50,000th resident and the city's 25 year anniversary.
  - Unmarked Black Binder #4: Early Reston Promotional Ads, 1970-71 (Shelf 1, Binder 4)
    This binder contains multiple advertisement clippings from the early days of Reston. Among them are ads promoting land and house sales, the large amount of acreage and townhomes available in Reston and the many ammenities it has such as golf, tennis, horseback riding, among others. Many ads in this binder also call attention to the nearby Wolf Trap ampitheatre.
  - Unmarked Black Binder #5: Reston Promotional Ads, Late-1970s and Early-1980s (Shelf 1, Binder 5)
    This binder contains multiple advertisement clippings from the late-1970s and early-1980s. Among them are ads promoting homes, low energy costs, good schools and the amount of treeage in Reston. One ad even calls attention to the fact that Reston was then the home of many Washington Redskins players and coaches. Also included in this binder are development plans for Reston's Center for Industry and Government and Commuter Bus system. There are also Reston Residential Land Sales and Industryal Land sales newsletters in this binder.
  - Unmarked Black Binder #6: Reston Promotional Ads, 1982-1984 (Shelf 1, Binder 6)
    This binder contains multiple advertisement clippings from the early-1980s. Among them are ads promoting homes, community and the neighborhood feel in Reston. Several ads also tout the creation of Dulles Toll Road, called "Reston expressway," selling a "20-minute" commute into DC.
  - Oversized Manila Folder #1, 1980s (Shelf 1, Folder 1)
    This binder contains extra copies of large advertisements from the 1980s that are included in the unmarked black binders on this same shelf.
  - Oversized Manila Folder #2, 1980s (Shelf 1, Folder 2)
    This binder contains extra copies of advertisements from the 1980s that are included in the unmarked black binders on this same shelf.
  - Reston Town Center binder #1, unknown date (Shelf 2, Binder 1)
    This binder is labeled "The Master Plan" for the building of the Reston Town Center in Reston, Va. It includes a map of the region and model photos of businesses in the Town Center including several of the Hyatt hotel planned for the Center. This binder also includes future growth projections for the city of Reston.
  - Reston Town Center binder #2, unknown date (Shelf 2, Binder 2)
    This binder is also labeled "The Master Plan" for the building of the Reston Town Center in Reston, Va. It includes insprations for the Town Center such as Rossyln and Balston, Va.; plus maps of the region and model photos of businesses in the Town Center including several of the Hyatt hotel planned for the Center along with the Offices at Fountain Square. This binder also includes future growth projections for the city of Reston.
  - Reston Town Center binder #3, unknown date (Shelf 2, Binder 3)
    This binder is also labeled "The Master Plan" for the building of the Reston Town Center in Reston, Va. It includes maps of the region and model photos of businesses in the Town Center including several of the Hyatt hotel planned for the Center along with the Offices at Fountain Square. This binder also includes future growth projections for the city of Reston.
  - Reston, Va. binder (maroon colored): Early Reston Ads, 1966-69 (Shelf 2, Binder 4)
    This binder contains multiple advertisement clippings from the very early days of Reston. Among them are ads promoting homes and the sporting and outdoor activities in Reston. Several ads also point to the proximity of Reston to D.C. via new roads such as Route 7 and the retention of wilderness and nature in Reston.
  - Unnamed Blue Binder #1: Housing Purchases Ledger, 1980s (Shelf 2, Binder 5)
    This binder includes housing and office purchases, broker information and contract prices from Reston in the early- to mid-1980s.
  - Unnamed Blue Binder #2: Housing Purchases Ledger, 1980s (Shelf 2, Binder 6)
    This binder includes housing purchases (townhomes, single family dwellings, condos, etc.), broker information and contract prices from Reston throughout the 1980s.
  - Unnamed Black Binder: Housing Purchases Ledger, 1980s (Shelf 2, Binder 7)
    This binder includes housing and office purchases, broker information and contract prices from Reston in the mid- to late-1980s.